[
    {
        "question": "notice period in Mastech Infotrellis",
        "answer": "The notice period is 90 days."
    },
    {
        "question": "work from home policy in Mastech Infotrellis",
        "answer": "Employees can work remotely 3 days a week."
    },
    {
        "question": "Webclock",
        "answer": "employees working from home should log their attenance in Webclock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lead HR in Mastech Infotrellis",
        "answer": "Neha suresh Kumar, EMAILID: neha.kumar@mastechdigital.com"
    },
    {
        "question": "ODC allowance",
        "answer": "Rs. 750 allowance + One-way cab drop"
    },
    {
        "question": "Upcoming CEO visit in Chennai",
        "answer": "30/06/2025"   
    },
    {
        "question":"Doubts related to Data Science or Point of Contact for Data Science GTM",
        "answer": "Contact - Sachin Navin Dedhia (Email : sdedhia@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Senior Director - Data Act & Analytics) and Deepti Soni(Email : deepti.soni@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Director Data Science & Analytics)"
    },
    {
        "question":"when I should submit the Timesheet in a week",
        "answer" : "New deadline is before Friday 12pm"
    },
    {
        "question":"Doubts related to Trainings, Learning & Development(L&D), External certification cost, Certification Reimbursement",
        "answer":"Contact - Adil Dar (Email : adil.dar@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Senior Manager - L&D), Deivanai Varavan(Email : deivanai.vairavan@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Training Specialist), Dolly Santra (Email : dollysantra.i@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Training Associate)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doubts related to Innovtion GTM or the Point of Contact for Innovation GTM",
        "answer" : "Contact - Shaik Magdhum Nawaz(Email : shaik.nawaz@mastechdigital.com)(Position : Director - Innovation)"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who is the Pre sales lead",
        "answer":"Subhopriyo Das, EmailID: subhopriyo.das@mastechdigital.com"
    },
    {
        "question":"who is the country head of Mastech Infotrellis, India / Senior Vice President & Head - Global delivery",
        "answer":"Lavanya Ramkumar, EmailID: lavanya@mastechdigital.com"
    }

]